<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="legal_notices_html">
<![CDATA[
<html>
<body>
<p><b><h1>Calendar Import/Export</h1></b></p>

<p>With some changes/additions 2021 by Thies Wellpott - no warrenty, use completely on your own risk.</p>

<p><tt>Copyright &#169; 2015 Jon Griffiths<br>
Copyright &#169; 2013 Dominik Schürmann<br>
Copyright &#169; 2010, 2011 Lukas Aichbauer</tt></p>

<p>Please see the <a href="https://github.com/sufficientlysecure/calendar-import-export">project page</a>
for full details and source code.</p>

<p>Based on <a href="https://code.google.com/p/ical-import-export/">ical-import-export</a> by Lukas
Aichbauer.  Includes <a href="https://github.com/ical4j/ical4j/>iCal4j</a> for iCalendar parsing.
Uses code from <a href="https://source.android.com/">The Android open source project</a> and
<a href="http://backport-jsr166.sourceforge.net/">backport-util-concurrent</a> in addition to
the apache project libraries <a href="https://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-codec/">commons-codec</a>,
<a href="https://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-lang/">commons-lang</a> and
<a href="https://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-logging/">commons-logging</a>.</p>

<p><b><h2>License</h2></b></p>

<p><tt>Calendar Import/Export is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.</tt></p>

<p><tt>Calendar Import/Export is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but <b>WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY</b>; without even the implied warranty of
<b>MERCHANTABILITY</b> or <b>FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE</b>.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.</tt></p>

<p><tt>You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with Calendar Import/Export.  If not, see
<a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>"http://www.gnu.org/licenses/</a>.</tt></p>

<p><b><h2>iCal4j license</h2></b></p>

<p><tt>Copyright &#169; 2013, Ben Fortuna</tt></p>
<p><tt>All rights reserved.</tt></p>

<p><tt>Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:</tt></p>

<p><tt>\to Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.</tt></p>

<p><tt>\to Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.</tt></p>

<p><tt>\to Neither the name of Ben Fortuna nor the names of any other contributors
may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
without specific prior written permission.</tt></p>

<p><tt>THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
\"AS IS\" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR
CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,
EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR
PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</tt></p>

<p><b><h2>AOSP and Apache library license</h2></b></p>

<p><tt>Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at</tt></p>

<p><tt>\t<a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0</a></tt></p>

<p><tt>Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an <b>\"AS IS\" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND</b>, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.</tt></p>

<p><b><h2>backport-util-concurrent license</h2></b></p>

<p><tt>This software is released to the public domain, in the spirit of the original
code written by Doug Lea. The code can be used for any purpose, modified, and redistributed
without acknowledgment. No warranty is provided, either express or implied.</tt></p>

</body>
</html>
]]>
</string>
</resources>
